A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Reproductive Health and Population (RHP), Reproductive Health Group, Staff Meeting Files FA691
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Reproductive Health and Population (RHP), Reproductive Health Group, Staff Meeting Files
1992-1995
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA691
1.31 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Arrangement
Chronological
Scope and Contents
Staff meeting notes, agendas and associated background materials.
- Mexico -- Reproductive Health Group -- Oaxaca Notes, May 1992 (Box 1)
- Mexico -- Reproductive Health Group -- Oaxaca -- Background Materials, 1992 (Box 1)
- RHP Staff Meeting -- Rio -- Staff Meeting Notes, 1993 (Box 1)
- RHP Staff Meeting -- Rio -- Memoranda, 1993 (Box 1)
- RHP Staff Meeting -- Rio -- Participant's Comments, 1993 (Box 1)
- RHP Staff Meeting -- Rio -- Site Visits and Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 1)
- RHP Staff Meeting -- Rio -- Agenda, 1993 (Box 1)
- RHP Meeting -- Lisbon -- Itinerary, 1994 (Box 1)
- RHP Meeting -- Lisbon -- Notes Draft #1, 1994 (Box 1)
- RHP Meeting -- Lisbon -- Meeting Evaluations, 1994 (Box 1)
- RHP Meeting -- Lisbon -- Notebook, 1994 (Box 1)
- RHP Meeting -- Lisbon -- Agenda -- 1st Round, 1994 (Box 1)
- RHP Meeting -- Lisbon -- Agenda -- 2nd Round, 1994 (Box 1)
- RHP Staff Meeting -- Athens -- Draft Agenda, 1995 (Box 1)
- RHP Staff Meeting -- Athens -- Background Materials, 1995 (Box 1)